Finding aid to Ruth Lee Kennedy papers CA.MA.00157 ======= Finding aid to Ruth Lee Kennedy papers CA.MS.00157 >>>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22
Smith College Archives
- Series V: Lecture and Research Notes, including related teaching activities
  - Drama of the Golden Age of Spanish literature - lecture notes for professionals and a slide presentation (no slides) (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">9)
  - Lecture notes - Various topics (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">10)
  - Notes to "Majiganga" (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">11)
  - Cervantes - Don Quixote - research and lecture notes (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">12)
  - Cervantes - general research notes and lectures (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">13)
  - Course notes and exams for University of Arizona Spanish 399 - Drama of the "Siglo del Oro" - Lope de Vega (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">14)
  - Research notes on Lope de Vega - life and works (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">15)
  - Research and lecture notes on Tirso de Molina - life and works (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">16)
  - Research notes for and drafts of RLK's article - "La prudencia en la jujer" y el ambiente quella produjo, 1940s (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">17)
  - Research notes - various topics (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">18-19)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 3, >>>>>> 9513965d9df0c493d3fef1502b8c9358307d0a22 type="folder">20)